{"status":"Success","data":[{"question":"\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d39\u0d4c\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \"100 most influential in UK-india relations :celebrating women \" \u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d09\u0d7e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ","answer":"Nirmala seetharam"},{"question":"Federation of indian export organisations (FIEO)\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d? ","answer":"Sarad kumar "},{"question":"\u0d09\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7c\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31 \u0d24\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d24\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f? ","answer":"Aatma nirbhar uttarpradesh Rojgar abhiyan "},{"question":"\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d02 2002 \u0d2d\u0d47\u0d26\u0d17\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02? ","answer":"Karnataka "},{"question":"2023 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d35\u0d47\u0d7e\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f? ","answer":"Australia &Newsland "},{"question":"2026 winter \u0d12\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3f? ","answer":"Italy "},{"question":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d35\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d40\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d38\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d24\u0d3f? ","answer":"New Life "},{"question":"\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d35\u0d40\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d1c\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d? ","answer":"Parvez Jamasji "},{"question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d32 \u0d26\u0d43\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d35\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d40\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d48\u0d2c\u0d7c \u0d12\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d31\u0d47\u0d37\u0d7b ","answer":"Operation P Hunt "},{"question":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d4d 19 \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d36\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d38\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d43\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d02\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d24\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26 \u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f? ","answer":"Kerala Dialogue "}],"code":"100"}
